Ben: Hey, yeah.
I’m on my way.
What’s the best way to get to the bar?
Izzy: By Tube.
Get the Piccadilly line westbound to King’s Cross.
Ben: OK, and then?
Izzy: Then change to the Victoria line southbound and get off at Warren Street.
It’s only two stops.
Ben: Could you say that again?
Izzy: Get the Piccadilly line westbound to King’s Cross.
Then change to the Victoria line southbound and get off at Warren Street.
It’s only two stops.
Ben: Where’s the bar?
Izzy: Turn right out of the station,
then go straight on about fifty metres and take the second right.
That’s Grafton Way.
The place is on the left.
It’s called The Conversation Bar.
Ben: Got it, thanks.
See you soon.
Izzy: And Ben…
Ben: Yeah…
Izzy: Please don’t be late.